Tawk Cin

Lewisville, TX 75067 (972) 998-6568 tawkcin99@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/tawk-cin/

Recent graduates of an intensive IT program focused on developing skills in technical support resulting in obtaining the Google IT Support Professional Certificate. 5+ years of experience in customer-facing roles have led to developed skills in communication, customer service, and client management.

RELEVANT SKILLS

Microsoft Office 365 • Technical Support & Troubleshooting • Ticketing System

User Training & Support • Operating Systems Installation • Software Installation & Configuration

Customer Service • Data Entry • Power User • Web developing, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL

• Troubleshooting computer hardware and software • Basic Programming Skill, Java, Python

EDUCATION

Merit America (Amazon Career Choice)

Google IT Support Professional Certificate

Skill development includes troubleshooting, customer service, networking, operating systems including Linux OS, systems administration, and security — all the fundamentals of IT support that are critical for success in the workplace; aligns with the objectives covered by the newly updated CompTIA A+ certification

Additional Skill Development

 Completed hands-on coursework covering Microsoft 365, Excel, Windows 10, ServiceNow ticketing system, fundamental cloud concepts, and PC maintenance and performance

Springboard (Amazon Career Choice)

Software Development Career

11/15/2023

Coursera

• Google IT Automation with Python Certificate

08/15/2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Transportation Associate TA (L3) • *Amazon, Texas*

05/2021-Present

- Check in and check out incoming and outgoing semi-trailer trucks using computer systems
- Moving trailers in the yard
- Utilizes various computer applications to manage loads arrival and departure for yard processes

Inbound | Outbound | Gate Keeper | Problem Solver | Ambassador • Amazon, Indiana and Texas

07/2015-07/2020

- Performing to meet business requirements
- Effectively fixed data errors for Amazon products and updated with the correct information for customers will receive the correct item in their order
- · Resolving inventory issues as best as possible to keep inventories defect clear
- To train new hire personals (associates)

IT Support Specialist • Siri, Malaysia

07/2011-07/2014

- Installed computer network devices, hardware and software for customers
- Troubleshooting computer issues and problem solved for any issues that arose within the company
- Setting up local network for individual homes
- Utilizes Windows OS and Mac OS and Linux (Ubuntu) to support business operations